Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Soccer
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting soccer
1955-1997
RU 1030
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
(5 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, score books, photographs, and publications documenting soccer at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, score books, photographs, and publications documenting soccer at Yale.
College athletes; College sports; Soccer; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students
- Records of the soccer team, 1955-1997; Accession 2006-A-139
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by topic.
  - Records of the men's team
    - European trip, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12 - 13)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Manager's report, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Player evaluations, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Post season
      - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Records of the women's team
    - General
      - 1986-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Personnel, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Scorebooks
    - Men's, 1968-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30 - 55)
    - Women's, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Photographs
    - Men's team
      - 1997 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - No date (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - European trip, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 59 - 60)
    - Women's team, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Publications
    - Men
      - Media Guides
        - 1968-1977 (Box 5, Folder 62)
        - 1978-1987 (Box 5, Folder 63)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 64)
        - 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Programs, etc., 1978-1988 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Women, 1979-1997 (Box 5, Folder 67)